

# OUSSEMA CHAIEB

SENIOR INTERNET OF THINGS TECHNICIAN

#### **PROFILE**

My name is chaieb oussema, I am 22 years old, I am a senior technician in the Internet of Things. I am a responsible man who always seeks to improve my skills. I have the spirit of working in groups and leading them because of my experiences in social and sports clubs. In fact, i am a professionel taekwondo athlete and an amateur trainer. I Just love to code and learn new things. I am a future full-stuck developer

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

**Birthdate** 07/05/2000

Gender Male

**Nationality** Tunisie

driver license car

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2020 - 2020

Adenium

electronic technician, sfax

I was carried out with the technical team which is responsible for the security such as the installation of surveillance cameras, alarms, etc.

2021 - 2021

**TOP SOFT** 

developper, sfax

I was concerned to create a patient management software for a dental office

2022 - 2022

**CONDORI** 

developper, sfax

I worked with the development team to create a software, website and mobile application that they use to manage stock, invoicing, online sales, delivery, admin panel, statistics, etc.

### **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2022

license: Internet of things

ENET'COM. SFAX

I had my License in Internet of Things in 2022. I was concerned to study web, software and mobile development. This training gave me the basic knowledge of objects: mathematics, telecommunications, electronics, conceptual, networks, IT necessary for the development of applications, databases, etc.

#### SKILLS

#### **SKILLS**

html/css php data base java script iava C# lua



#### **LANGUAGE**

arabic Frensh English



#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **Achievement**

i made a lot of site web for restaurents, cafes, communités with apply applications.



i made a mobile application for delivery boys but i believe i can make better

I created a stock management includes facturation, warehouse and employee management

## **INTERESTS**

Interest full-stuck developer

## **HOBBIES**

- traveling
- sports
- video games

## **QUALITIES**

- Responsable
- i learn fast
- I have the spirit of working in a team

# **CERTIFICATE**

java

## **CONTACT**

- **TUNISIE**
- **L** +216 50 289 903
- ✓ oussemachaieb7@gmail.com

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.